Alice in Terrorland is a horror, thriller film directed by Richard John Taylor.
A recently bereaved teenage girl goes to live with her aunt in a secluded
woodland house, unaware that sinister forces lurk within.
Alice, played by Lizzy Willis.
Beth, played by Rula Lenska.
The Mad Hatter, played by Jon-Paul Gates.
The Rabbit, played by Steve Wraith.
The Twins, played by Lila Sarner.
The Smoking Man, played by Nigel Troup.
Rula Lenska (born Roza Maria Leopoldyna Lubienski 30
September 1947) is a British actress.
She mainly appears in British stage and television productions and is known in the United
States for a series of television advertisements in the 1970s and 1980s.
She is known for the films Queen Kong and Aura, and she portrayed
Claudia Colby in the ITV soap opera Coronation Street.
Lenska was married to the actors Brian Deacon
(1977–1987) and Dennis Waterman (1987–1998).
Both marriages ended in divorce.
The film explores themes of bereavement, teenage girl, independent film.
The tone is dark and intense.